(Penny:)It's the comic book store,
it's the comic bookstore,
it's the comic book store!
(Penny:)-It's the comic book store.
-Oh!
(Leonard:)-Do you think Penny's mad at me?
-Because you're in the right lane
behind a bus and won't go around it?
I'm sure she finds it charming.
(Leonard:)No, because I didn't
want heron my team.
(Bernadette:)I'm starting to think
she dodged a bullet.
(Bernadette:)The slowest bullet in the world.
(Leonard:)I never realized
you were so competitive.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, I know.
(Bernadette:)It's probably because I grew up
with five brothers and sisters
so I had to tight for every--
(Bernadette:)Oh, my God, you did not
just slow down for a bird!
You know they fly, right?!